<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="botonHoteles">Hotels</string>
    <string name="botonRestaurantes">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="botonSitios">tourist sites</string>

    <string name="app_name">SanRafa</string>
    <string name="titulohomehoteles">Hotels in Peñol</string>
    <string name="descripcionhomehoteles">In our town, you will find accommodations ranging from 35000 COP
        to luxurious cabins equipped with all the elements to promote a restorative rest.</string>
    <string name="botonhomehoteles">See hoteles</string>

    <string name="titulohomerestaurantes">Restaurants in Peñol</string>
    <string name="descripcionrestaurantes">Due to Antioquia department integrating flavours from different
        parts of the world and the variety of local ingredients for its cuisine, it can be ensured
        that visitors will fall in love with Antioquia culinary delights. </string>
    <string name="botonhomerestaurantes">see Restaurants</string>

    <string name="titulohomesitios">tourist sites</string>
    <string name="descripcionresitios">The stillness of the blue and clear skies of the Antiquia peninsula,
      area of northeastern Colombia, is interrupted by bright pink flowers that dissolve
        in spirals over the lagoons . </string>

    <string name="nombre">David Salzar Saldarriaga</string>
    <string name="acercaDe">Musico y programador y actualmente
en proceso de formación como Técnico en
Desarrollo de Software. Combino la creatividad
visual con conocimientos técnicos para crear
experiencias únicas. Mi perl abarca desde el

diseño gráco hasta la programación, destacán-
dome en el área de desarrollo Front end. Poseo

competencias laborales de dinamismo, creativi-
dad y atención al detalle, fundamentales para

impulsar proyectos hacia el siguiente nivel.</string>

    <string name="opcion1">English</string>
    <string name="opcion2">Spanish</string>
    <string name="opcion3">French</string>
    <string name="opcion4">Review</string>
    <string name="opcion5">About us</string>

    <string name="titulohomeresena2">History of El Peñol </string>

    <string name="historiamanaure">"According to oral tradition, Peñol owes its name to the radiance
        of a high-born indigenous individual who bequeathed his name to this geographical site.
        According to research, indeed, in the neighboring Republic of Venezuela, there was an indigenous
        chief of the Caquetío tribe with much prestige who went by the name of Peñol. Initially,
        this indigenous person was very friendly with the conquistadors and the evangelizers,
        but later he confronted the Spaniards and in 1821 was assassinated by Morillos army.

        The Municipality of Peñol was created by ordinance 015 of 1973, which began to take effect
        on October 1, 1974. This date is institutionalized to celebrate Peña anniversary.
        This ordinance project was presented by Peña son and deputy, Manuel Mengual Meza,
        and was sanctioned by Dr. Benjamín Armenta López, Governor of the Department of Antioquia.</string>
</resources>